我叫巴里·艾伦
My name is Barry Allen,
是现今世上速度最快的人
and I am the fastest man alive.
在外人看来
To the outside world,
我只是个普通的鉴证专员
I'm an ordinary forensic scientist,
但在尖端科研实验室的朋友们的帮助下
but secretly, with the help of my friends at S.T.A.R. Labs,
我秘密地打击犯罪  寻找跟我一样的超能力者
I fight crime and find other meta-humans like me.
但当我女儿从未来时空前来帮忙
But when my daughter came back from the future to help,
她改变了现在
she changed the present,
现在我们的世界比以往更加危险
and now our world is more dangerous than ever,
我是唯一一个来得及拯救世界的人
and I'm the only one fast enough to save it.
我是闪电侠
I am the Flash.
《闪电侠》前情回顾
Previously on "The Flash"...
咱们跳舞吧  小蛐蛐
Let's dance, crickets-y.
她怎么还能出来
How can she still come out?
因为她对蝉的匕首免疫
Because she's immune to Cicada's dagger?
那碎片并没有抑制我的超能力
The shards weren't dampening my powers.
而是在移除他们
They were removing them.
我们能做治愈超能力者的解药
We could make a meta-human cure.
-这是什么  -那是什么  诺拉的日记
- What this is? - What is that, Nora's journal?
你之前见过这种代码吗
Have you seen this code before?
见过  就在巴里从神速力里出来之后
Yeah, right after Barry came out of the Speed Force.
-这是一种时间语言  -时间语言吗
- It's a time language. - Time language?
这种语言要从哪学习呢
Where does one learn something like that?
-事实上是我发明的  -聪明的姑娘
- I created it, actually. - Clever girl.
我的天  奥林
My God, Orlin.
你快吓死我了
You scared the living daylights out of me.
有人跟着你吗
Did anyone follow you?
当然没有
Of course not.
你在医院和闪电侠交手已经过去好几周了
It's been weeks since you fought the Flash at the hospital.
如果有人知道你在这
If anyone knew you were here,
你现在肯定已经被找到了
you would have found out by now.
我给你带了些生活用品
I got you some groceries
还有美洛昔康用于你的伤口
and some Meloxicam for your injuries.
我不需要
I don't need it.
很好
Good to hear.
-格蕾丝怎么样了  -没什么变化
- How's Grace? - Nothing's changed.
她很稳定  中城警局还没走
She's stable. CCPD hasn't left
他们一时半会也走不了
and they're not leaving any time soon.
-我得看看她  -不可能
- Well, I need to see her, Doc. - That's not possible.
别告诉我什么是可能的
Don't tell me what's possible.
你生气了  很好
You're angry. Good.
鉴于你家人在超能力者手中
For all the pain your family has suffered
所承受的所有痛苦  你应该生气
at the hands of those metas, you should be.
但现在你没什么能为格蕾丝做的
But right now there isn't anything you can do for Grace,
所以把怒火冲着其他东西发吧
so put that anger towards something else.
我有个朋友
I have a friend who feels the same way
和我们对超能力者的看法一样
about meta-humans as we do,
他想帮助你完成你未完成的事情
and he wants to help you finish what you've started.
中城警局 2018年超能力者逮捕记录
奥林
Orlin?
是时候回去工作了
It's time to get back to work.
就是这了  我们和目标之间只隔
This is it. The only thing between us
一堵钢筋混凝土墙
and our big score is one reinforced concrete wall.
-别伤到自己  博克  -不会伤到博克的
Don't hurt yourself, Bork. - Can't hurt Bork.
但博克会伤到你
But Bork can hurt you.
这就行了
That should do it.
怎么回事
The hell?
你也是超能力者
You're one, too.
闪 电 侠
第五季
第十一集
我不知道哪个更疯狂  这家伙这么大个
I don't know what's crazier, how big this guy is
还是他身上有这么多刀伤
or the number of incised wounds on his body.
凹陷性颅骨骨折表明
Well, and the depressed skull fracture points to impact
硬化表面受到巨大冲击
with hardened surface,
但死因绝对是连续多次刀伤
but cause of death is definitely repeated stabbings.
没错  看起来有人特别生气
Yeah, looks like someone was really angry.
看这些伤口
Look at these wounds.
看起来是不是和路霸身上的伤口
Doesn't it look like they have the same depth and diameter
大小深度一样
as the ones on Gridlock's body?
对  和方块和蕾琳·夏普的也一样
Yeah, and like Block's and Raelene Sharp's.
没错
Yeah.
爱瑞丝接到线报
Iris just got a tip.
又一个超能力者在自己公寓被害  同样的死因
Another meta-human was murdered in her apartment, same COD.
-爸  这不是个别案件  -的确不是
- Dad, these aren't one offs. - No.
蝉回来了  他在疯狂屠杀
Cicada's back and he's on a killing spree.
这些袭击其中一个肯定有线索
Okay, well, there's got to be a lead in one of these attacks
能帮我们追踪到他  我们让小队去调查
that can help us track him. We'll get the team on it.
冰霜杀手  不是吧  我受不了了
Killer Frost, seriously? I can't take it anymore.
凯特琳  一切还好
Uh, Caitlin, is everything-
和另一个你的谈话
Alter-ego confab.
看了太多集《姐妹  姐妹》
Seen enough episodes of "Sister, Sister"
我一看到姐妹间口角就能辨别
to recognize a sibling spat when I see one.
我正帮西斯科研发超能力者解药
So, I'm trying to help Cisco with his meta-human cure,
但每次我开始做
but every time I start working on it,
冰霜杀手就出现  弄乱我的方程式
Killer Frost takes over and messes with my equations.
像这样
Like this.
她把我所有的杂合子都改成了星号
She changed all my heterozygotes into asterisks.
我以为这些是小雪花
Oh, I thought those were just tiny snowflakes.
所以她不合作
So she's not on board?
是的  我也不知道为什么
No, and I don't exactly know why.
-你不能直接问她吗  -问过了
- Can't you just ask her? - Oh, I've tried.
但每次我们开始聊这个话题
But every time we start talking about it,
她就开始唱巴尼的《我爱你》那首歌
she starts singing Barney's "I Love You" song.
-还真是冷酷啊  -嗯
- Ooh, that's cold. - Yeah.
那西斯科呢  他有什么新发现吗
What about Cisco? Is he having any luck?
还没有
Not yet.
他去了唐豪瑟站点  这样他就可以专心做事
He went to the Tannhauser off-sites so he could concentrate.
他说那里很安静
He says it's quiet there.
安静得像个墓穴
Yeah. Quiet like a tomb.
我认为如果我能把连接着人类DNA
So I think if I can isolate the genetic marker
与暗物质的遗传标记分离出来
that bonds human DNA to dark matter,
我就能逆向还原这个过程
I can reverse engineer the process
拆解开  制出解药
and unravel it to create a cure.
-好极了  -但是我需要尚未与暗物质
- That's great. - Yeah, except I need meta-DNA
完全结合在一起的超能力者DNA才行
that hasn't fully bonded with dark matter yet.
当然了  因为我们都知道
Of course, because as we all know
由于基因改造  我们...  为什么
with genetic modification we-- Why?
因为只有那次我能确定
Because that's the only time when I can identify
标记存在于基因组里
where the marker is in the genome.
所以你需要最近新生的超能力者DNA吗
Okay, so you need DNA from a meta-human who was created recently?
是的  过去八个月内的最好
Yeah, ideally in the last eight months,
但我能想到的所有人都被蝉杀死了
but everyone I can think of has been killed by Cicada.
好吧
Right.
那我们要去哪里找呢
So where the heck do we look?
诺拉·韦斯特·艾伦日记里唯一解密的标题
The lone decrypted entry from the journal of Nora West Allen:
"时间线是有延展性的"
"The timeline is malleable."
为什么只翻译了这个标题
Why that's the only one that translated?
她为什么对时间线这么感兴趣
And why is she interested in the timeline,
也许更重要的是
and maybe more important,
她为什么要隐瞒自己对此感兴趣呢
why is she hiding this interest?
歇洛克  我们需要你来一下表层控制室
Sherloque, we need you in the cortex.
当然
But of course.
基拉·梅  德韦恩·盖斯特和卡尔·博克
Kira May, Dwayne Geist, Carl Bork.
三名超能力者昨晚全遭到了蝉的毒手
All three metas who were killed by Cicada last night.
蝉过去12个小时之内杀的人
So Cicada's killed almost as many people
几乎和过去八个月之内杀的一样多
in the last 12 hours as he has in the last eight months?
看来他并没有打算减缓杀戒
And it doesn't look like he's slowing down anytime soon.
在他再伤人之前  我们要阻止他
Well, we need to stop him before he hurts anyone else.
歇洛克  你有什么建议吗
Sherloque, do you have any ideas on what to do about that?
目前没有
Not at the moment,
但我每次在调查中遇到瓶颈时
but any time I run into a road block in an investigation,
我总是会这么做
I do what I always do.
另辟蹊径
I just pursue a different avenue.
我们会找到他的  会有什么把他带过来的
We'll find him. Something will bring him to us.
比如...
Something like--
卫星捕捉到暗物质耀斑  是他
Satellites picking up dark matter flare. It's him.
比如说这个
Something like that.
换上战衣  我们的时间不多
Suit up. We don't have a lot of time.
防范于未然  这个给冰霜杀手
Not without precautions. For Killer Frost.
她不需要武器  冰霜杀手本身就是武器
She doesn't need a weapon. Killer Frost is the weapon.
不管你是否有超能力  我都会灭了你
Powers or no powers, I will mess you up.
用这个消除
Negate this!
坚持住  帮忙
Hold on. Help!
我们需要凯特琳
We need Caitlin.
我们要送她去医院
We need to get her to a hospital.
来  跟我走
Here, come with me.
天呐
Oh God.
不要
No!
诺拉  诺拉  诺拉
Nora. Hey, Nora, Nora?
诺拉  诺拉
Okay, Nora-- Nora?
诺拉
Nora?
情况如何
Well?
蝉造成她的第三  第四及第五节腰椎
Cicada caused an axial burst fracture
轴向破裂骨折
in her L3, L4, and L5 vertebrae.
同时还造成她的第四胸椎严重移位
He also severely displaced her fourth thoracic vertebrae.
情况不乐观
It's not good.
但是她会开始极速痊愈的对吧
But her speed healing is going to kick in, right?
对吧
Right?
蝉用暗物质一刀刺入她的身体里
Cicada's cut flooded her body with dark matter.
这会影响到她的超能力
It's affecting her powers.
她的极速恢复会暂时...
Her speed healing should kick in...
起作用的
for now.
我会继续监控她的情况
I'll keep monitoring her progress.
-巴里  -没事  她会恢复的
- Barry. - It's okay, she'll heal.
不会有事的
It'll be all right.
诺拉
Nora?
出什么事了
Oh, what happened?
亲爱的
Honey, um...
为什么呼吸会痛
Oh, why does it hurt to breathe?
会痛一阵子
It's gonna hurt for a little bit.
为什么
Why?
我的脚动不了
I can't move my legs.
我的脚为什么动不了
Um, why can't I move my legs?
-妈  我的脚动不了  -诺拉
- Mom, I can't move my legs. - Nora.
妈  妈  为什么我的脚动不了
Mom? Mom, why can't I move my legs?
诺拉  听着
Nora, look.
你的脚动不了是因为
You can't move your legs because...
蝉刺伤了你的背
Cicada broke your back.
什么  我瘫痪了吗
What? So I'm paralyzed?
-是永久的吗  -不不是永久的
- What, forever? - No, no, not forever.
那要多久
Well, for how long then?
我们不知道
We don't know.
妈妈
Mom...
我尽快赶来了
Hey, I got here as fast as I could.
乔还在西藏
Joe's still in Tibet.
我给他留言让他尽快赶来了
I left him a message to get back ASAP.
没事的  他应该和沃利在一起
Hey, it's all right. He should stay with Wally.
我的天
Oh, my God.
-她怎么样了  -不太好
- How is she? - It's not good.
真令人难过  巴里
I'm so sorry, Barry.
我不在乎用什么办法
Hey, I don't care how we do it.
-我们必须马上阻止德韦恩  -我同意
- We need to stop Dwyer now. - Well, I agree.
好吧 我去告诉西斯科
All right, Well, I'm gonna call Cisco.
应该把他叫回来
We should get him back here.
不不  他应该先完成他那解药
No, no, no, he-he should finish the cure he's working on.
他在那里比较有用
His time is better spent there.
-歇洛克  -什么
- Sherloque. - Oui?
该你表现了  我们怎么追踪这家伙
Earn your money. How do we track this guy?
我认为我们首先要做的
Well, I think the first thing we should do
就是专注调查受害者  找出联系
is concentrate on the victims. Look for a connection.
看看这个例子  这人叫盖斯特
Take a look here for example. This man, Geist,
他脖子上有蜘蛛纹身
has a spider tattoo on his neck,
一般是暗示被缠在了网中
generally indicating he was caught in some form of web.
什么样的网  或许是监狱网
What kind of web? A prison web, perhaps.
基拉·梅  她穿着衣服
And Kira May-She was wearing clothes.
她当然穿着衣服了  呆子
Of course she was wearing clothes, Giraffe.
不是  她穿的衣服比她要大两码
No, she was wearing clothes that are two sizes too large.
大两码  近期体重剧降
Two sizes too large. Recent rapid weight loss.
是单独拘禁的常见影响
It's a common side effect of solitary confinement.
对  还有卡尔·博克
Right. And Carl Borg--
还有卡尔·博克  这个报告说他眼皮下垂
And Carl Borg, this report says he had a droopy eyelid
也就是神经虚弱
which is nerve paralysis,
喝太多波拉特的后果
common side effect of consuming too much Borat.
或者这个地球叫做布鲁诺
Or as it's known on this earth, Bruno.
通常被叫做监狱酒
More commonly known as prison wine.
监狱酒
Prison wine.
这些超能力者都是前罪犯
All three of these meta-humans were former criminals.
看看这个
Look at this.
这是2018年的超能力者逮捕列表
It's a meta-human arrest log from 2018.
看看前三个名字
Look at the first three names.
都是他的受害者
These were his victims.
他在按照名单杀人
He's killing in the order of this list.
名单有地址  工作信息
This list has addresses, employment information.
还有车牌号  这里有一切
It's got license plate numbers. This is everything
蝉找到他们所需要的资料
Cicada needs to find them.
他是怎么搞到这些的
Where would he even get this?
我觉得只有一个地方可能  对吧
I think there's only one place, right?
我们城市里还有个杀手在逃
There's a killer still at large in our city.
人们害怕走在街上
People are afraid of being out in the streets.
我一天接到上百个关于这家伙的电话
I'm getting 100 phone calls a day about this guy.
我要你们重新搜查街区
I want neighborhoods re-canvassed.
我要重新调查证物  乔西
I want evidence re-examined. Jonesy!
带上你的小队去城里贴德韦恩的照片
Take your unit and paper the city with Dwyer's photo.
我要抓到这家伙  开始行动吧
I want this guy. Let's go get him!
艾伦
Allen?
我们需要谈谈  私下谈
We need to talk... in private.
好吧
All right.
这是什么
What the hell is this?
这是德韦恩找受害者的方式
That's how Dwyer's getting his victims.
这是我们超能力者数据库里的吗
This is from our database of meta-humans?
没有证据显示他是从中城警局搞到的
Well, it doesn't prove he got it from CCPD.
是吗
Doesn't it?
他或许是侵入了其他分局
He could have broken into another precinct
或是黑入中城警局数据库拿到的
or hacked into the CCPD database.
大卫  德韦恩是机械工  不是黑客
David Dwyer is a machinist. He's not a hacker.
有人给了他这个  这里的人
Somebody gave this to him. Somebody here!
好吧  巴里  也许我们该让
Okay, Barry, maybe we should go ahead
辛格队长自己去调查这事
and let Captain Singh look into this on his own.
我觉得这是个好主意
Yeah, I think that's a good idea.
谢谢  大卫
Thank you, David.
巴里  巴里
Hey, Barry. Barry.
巴里  你要去哪
Barry, where are you going?
我不知道  塞西尔
I don't know, Cecile,
但我得做点什么
but I gotta do something
赶在德韦恩杀掉那名单上的所有人之前
before Dwyer kills all the people on that list.
如果我们也用它呢
What if we use it, too?
-什么  -那名单
- What? - The list.
三年前  乔请我帮着将一个超能力者
Three years ago, Joe asked me to help get meta-humans
转移出这个城市
transferred out of the city.
我记得  你告诉他不要这么做
Yeah, I remember. You told him not to do it.
是  那是在我知道现在这一切之前
Yeah, well, that was before I knew what I know now.
再说  那些超能力者是现行犯人
Besides, those metas were active prisoners.
而这些超能力者  他们已经服刑过了
These metas, they've already served their time.
即使我们把他们送出城  也没有意义
Look, even if we got 'em out of town, it wouldn't matter.
蝉最终还是能追踪到他们
Cicada's gonna track them down eventually.
他们需要换新名字  新身份
They need new names, new identities.
我们没有资源去办这件事
We don't have the resources to do that.
我们是没有
No, we do not.
但是联调局有
But the Feds do.
他们一直以来都给普通人提供保护
They give this kind of protection to regular humans all the time.
他们也是时候该保护超能力者了
It is about time they start offering it to meta-humans, too.
我打算去召集我以前帮助过的所有人
I am going to go call in every favor I have ever banked
然后去实现这件事
and I am going to make this thing happen,
与此同时
and in the meantime,
你要把他们带到安全的地方
you need to go get them somewhere safe.
-行  -好的
- All right. - Okay.
你可以尝试一下扭动脚趾吗
So, can you try wiggling your toes?
办不到
I can't.
再来一次
Again?
我不行
I can't.
有感觉吗
Anything?
我什么都感觉不到
I don't feel anything.
好吧  蝉的暗物质已经从你的体内清除
Okay, well, Cicada's dark matter has left your system,
所以你应该能很快恢复
so you should be healing soon.
自从上一次的扫描之后
I mean, since my last scan,
你的脊髓轴突已经生长了五毫米
your spinal axons have grown five millimeters.
这算很不错了  对吗
That's something, right?
这是进步
It's progress.
也许不是我们所希望的愈合速度
Maybe not quite the speed we were hoping for,
但算很不错了
but it's something.
我要去做多几次化验
I'm going to go run a few more tests.
不要放弃  好吗
Don't give up, okay?
生长就是生长了
Growth is growth.
正常的轴突生长率
Normal axon growth rate
在大神经里一天能生长五毫米
reaches five millimeters a day in a large nerve.
加上极速恢复
With speed healing,
我的轴突生长应该超过一百毫米
mine should be over 100.
你怎么知道的
How do you know that?
我五年级的时候上过神经再生的课
I took neuro-regeneration in my fifth grade STEM class.
我五年级的时候学的是分数
I took fractions in fifth grade.
如果我无法恢复怎么办  妈妈
What if I don't heal, Mom?
如果我再也好不起来了怎么办
What if I never get better?
可以让我自己一个人呆一会吗
Can I just be left alone for a little bit, please?
好  好的
Yeah. Okay.
我尊重你对解药抗议的权利  小冰霜
I respect your right to protest the cure, Frosty,
但甚至对于我来说  这有点过头了
but even for me, that is excessive.
现在凯特琳可能会知道该怎么做了
Well, maybe Caitlin will get the hint now.
斯诺和冰霜有概念上的分歧
Snow and Frost are having creative differences.
我叫凯特琳来
I'll get Caitlin.
不  我需要你  实际上
No, I-I need you, actually.
我们需要在蝉找到超能力者之前
We need to get all those metas to a safe house
把他们都带到安全屋
before Cicada finds them.
然后你觉得他们会听从我的话吗
Oh, and you think they're going to listen to me?
一半对一半吧
50-50 on that.
我也没这么"名副其实"
I haven't quite lived up to my name.
但我确实知道我们应该从哪里入手
But I do know where we should start.
这里看起来不像几个月里有人呆过的样子
Doesn't look like anyone's been here in months.
关于阿姆内特出城的传闻可能是真的
Maybe the rumors about Amunet skipping town are true.
我们来这里不是为了阿姆内特
We're not here for Amunet.
我们是为了她的宠物蛇而来的
We're here for her pet snake.
关于蛇的习惯
And the thing about snakes is,
它们总是潜伏在黑暗的角落
they're always lurking in some dark corner.
你好啊  诺瓦克
Hello, Norvock.
冰霜  幸亏是你
Frost, thank God it's you.
这些是蝉的目标
Those are Cicada's targets,
但是我们需要你的帮助  集合所有人
but we need your help rounding everyone up
这样可以把他们送到安全的地方
so we can get them to safety.
他们不会相信一群带着面具的人的
Because they're not going to trust a bunch of masks?
他们会的  只要你告诉他们是为他们好
They will if you tell them it's for their own good.
其中有些令人讨厌的家伙
Some of these guys are bad news.
你确定他们值得解救吗
You sure they're worth saving?
你就是吗  蝉不会停止追捕
Are you? Cicada's not going to stop
直到这座城市的所有超能力者都死掉
until every meta in this city is dead.
这是你想要的下场吗
Is that how you want to end up?
该死  他对你做了什么
Damn. What did he do to you?
我们已经安排好所有人参加
We've arranged for everyone to enter
一个证人保护计划
a witness protection program.
今晚联邦探员会带你们离开城市去安全的地方
Federal agents will lead you out of the city to safety tonight.
好的
All right.
我加入  但前提是我是第一批转移的人
I'm in, but only if I'm the first one on that transport.
你为超能力者同伴们着想  真是太好了
Nice of you to look out for your fellow metas.
我只为我还有我自己着想
I look out for me and me alone.
那就开始召集大家吧
Then let's get to rounding up.
是的
Yup.
-大卫  -假如是为了那个名单
- David. - If this is about that list...
是的  但不是你想的那样
It is, but it's not what you think.
我需要你的帮助
I need your help.
帮什么忙
With what?
我有一批超能力者需要转移去联邦保护
I'm having those metas moved to federal protection,
这就是你要做的工作
which is where you come in.
你需要些什么
What do you need?
路障  今晚  从林辛大道到韦伯大道
Road blocks, tonight, from Linsin to Webber Avenue.
我知道  大卫  我知道
I know, David, I know,
但我不能冒险在预定好的转移中
but I can't risk any incoming traffic
出现交通状况
during the scheduled transfer.
我会做到的
I'll make it happen.
谢谢你
Thank you.
琼斯警官
Officer Jones.
你还好吗
You all right?
非常好
Never better.
我等得不耐烦了
I'm tired of waiting.
这个蝉  他想杀我们
This Cicada, he wants to kill us?
要我说  我们先杀掉他
I say we kill him first.
不行  我们是你唯一的机会
You can't. We're your only chance.
你一直这样说
So you keep saying.
如果你蠢到无法认清事实的话
Look, if you're too dumb to recognize the truth,
你可以走了  但是你要靠你自己
then you can go, but you're on your own.
我不会让其他任何人被这个疯子伤害到
I'm not going to watch anybody else be broken by this maniac.
他说的是实话
He's telling the truth.
我看到蝉杀了卡尔·博克
I saw Cicada kill Carl Bork.
博克死了
Bork's dead?
他的匕首会消除我们的超能力
His dagger took away our powers.
我逃跑了  但是博克留下战斗
I ran, Bork fought.
这就是为什么我在这里而他没有
That's why I'm here and he's not.
所以如果你们想离开的话就走
So, yeah, leave if you want,
但是我会听这些人的
but I'm gonna listen to these guys
继续活下去
and stay alive.
你刚刚的演讲很精彩
That was quite the speech back there.
听起来像是你真的想要
Almost seemed like you actually wanted
拯救那些超能力者
to save those meta-humans.
不  你知道我在想什么
No, you know me better than that.
不  我不知道
No, I don't think I do.
我以前是个好人
I used to be a good guy, you know?
我在中城动物园工作  看管爬行动物的笼子
I worked at the Central City Zoo, watching the reptile cage.
粒子加速器爆炸那天晚上我们在营业
We were open the night the particle accelerator blew up.
爆炸破坏了所有的笼子
After the blast shattered all the cages,
我把一条眼镜蛇从一个孩子身上拿开
I had to pull an elapid snake off a kid.
然后暗物质击中了我
Then that dark matter hit.
那个孩子怎么样了
What happened to the kid?
他没事
He's fine.
但是我得到了什么  在脑子里有一条蛇
But what do I get, huh? A snake in my head?
还有一个变态杀人犯想杀我
And a psycho killer that wants me dead?
那是我最后一次把别人的安危放在自己前面
That was the last time I put anyone else before myself.
似乎我心中的一小部分
You know, it's almost like a small part of me feels
为那个人感到遗憾
sorry for that guy.
为什么  他只是想保护自己
Why? He's only out for himself.
拜托  很明显他吓坏了
Come on, he's clearly terrified.
我知道那是什么感受
I know what that's like.
你要说你从未像他那样害怕过吗
You're going to tell me that you've never felt fear like that?
-没有  为什么  -真的吗
- No, why? - Really?
从来没担心过凯特琳在制作解药吗
Not even a little bit worried about Caitlin making the cure?
所有人都在这里吗
Is that everyone?
只有肖娜·贝兹不在
Everyone except Shawna Baez.
一个自称为躲猫猫的超能力者
A meta that calls herself Peek-A-Boo?
有人知道她在哪里吗
Anyone know where she'll be?
去第八大道的阳光美元酒吧试试
Try the Sundollar on Eighth.
好的
All right.
酒吧还没开门  你也不行  闪电侠
Bar's not open yet. Not even for you, Flash.
肖娜  我需要你跟我走
Shawna. I need you to come with me.
我这次什么也没做
I didn't do anything this time.
我知道  你没惹麻烦
I know. You're not in trouble.
你有危险
All right, you're in danger.
我想把你带到安全的地方
I want to take you some place safe.
比如你的科学监狱吗  抱歉
Like your science prison? Sorry.
肖娜  拜托了
Shawna? Please.
有人想要杀你
Somebody is trying to kill you.
总是有人要杀我
Someone's always trying to kill me.
再见  闪电侠
See ya around, Flash.
你对我做了什么
What did you do to me?
肖娜  快跑
Shawna, run.
那是谁
Who the hell is that?
拿上这个  按那个按钮
Take this, press the button.
缺口打开时跳进去
When a breach opens, jump into it.
快走
Go!
快点  快点
Come on, come on...
你来打开它
Make this thing work.
他们都很害怕  我能感受到
They're all terrified. I can feel it.
也许现在他们相信我们了
Maybe now they believe us.
我们就要成功了
Hey, we're almost through this.
我们会把所有人带到安全的地方
We are going to get all of these people to safety.
即使我们做到了  蝉也不会停止杀戮
Even if we do, Cicada's not going to stop killing.
-直到  -直到他死掉
- Not until-- - Until he's dead.
-我没这么说  -你不需要说出来
- I didn't say that. - You didn't have to.
我从你身上感受到的愤怒说明了一切
The anger that I feel from you says it all.
我应该感受到什么  他差点杀了诺拉
How am I supposed to feel? He almost killed Nora.
巴里  我理解  我真的理解
Barry, I understand, I do.
那个人伤害了你的孩子
That man hurt your child.
但是你现在感受到的愤怒
But this anger that you're feeling,
我曾经在蝉的身上
I have felt it before...
感受过
from Cicada.
亲爱的  如果你放任它  愤怒就会控制你
Honey, if you let it, this rage will consume you,
就像它已经控制了他那样
the same way it's already consumed him.
等等  我以前在别人身上感受过这种愤怒
Wait, I have felt this anger from someone before.
在中城警局  天哪  巴里
At CCPD. Oh, my God, Barry,
我想我知道是谁泄露了名单
I think I know who leaked the list.
我们去抓住他
Then let's go get him.
不  不行  你呆在这里
No, no, no, you-- you stay here.
你要把这些超能力者护送到转移点
You get these metas to the drop.
我能处理剩下的事
I can handle the rest.
神经充满愉悦啊
Ah, well, look. Neurological delight.
为什么  你马上就能康复
Why, you'll be back on these feet
然后来追捕蝉了
and chasing Cicada in no time.
希望如此
I hope so.
会的  或许你同时也可以来帮我
Yes. In the meantime, maybe you can help me do the same.
我已经把我知道的闪电侠博物馆的事
Oh, I already told the team everything I know
都告诉了小队
about the Flash museum.
闪电侠博物馆  是的
Flash museum, right.
你觉得我能看看闪电侠博物馆里的
Do you think that I could look at the archives
那些档案吗
from that Flash museum?
毕竟我的职业就是
After all, I have made a career
注意到别人错过的东西
out of noticing things that other people miss.
或许可以把那些档案带来
Maybe it's not a problem to bring those archives
给我看一下吗
for me to look at?
我觉得可以
ah, I guess so.
或者我过去会更方便一点
Or maybe it's easier for me to go there?
你想让我带你去未来吗
You want me to bring you to the future?
这主意不错
It's a great suggestion.
就算不是极速者也能
Is it even possible for a non-speedster
进入那个东西吗  你们叫做什么来着
to go into the commodity-- What'd you call it? The, um...
-神速力  -神速力  对
- The Speed Force? - Speed Force. Right.
我不确定
Uh, I'm not sure.
好吧
Right.
或许这要问更有经验的人
Well, perhaps that's a question for someone with more experience.
歇洛克
Sherloque.
我能和你谈一下吗
Can I talk to you for a second?
不好意思
Excusez-moi.
-那是我女儿  -是的  所以呢
- That's my daughter in there. - Yes, so?
我会不惜一切代价保护她
And I'm going to do whatever it takes to protect her.
即使是对待我以为是她朋友的人
Even from people who I thought were her friends.
所以你现在需要告诉我
So I'm gonna need you to tell me right now
你为什么在调查诺拉
why you're investigating Nora.
调查  不  不  什么
Invest--no, no. Quoi?
没人在调查诺拉
No one's investigating Nora.
什么  没人在调查诺拉
Quoi? No one's investigating Nora.
或许我调查了一点点诺拉
Maybe I'm investigating Nora a little bit.
为什么
Why?
你是觉得诺拉隐瞒了什么吗
You think, what, Nora is hiding something?
不是
No, um...
我该怎么说呢
How can I say this?
有时候你是个侦探
Sometimes when you're a detective,
你会发现故事然后追查下去
you see a story and you follow it.
存在着不同的路径
And there's different tracks.
你会沿着某条路走
You follow down the track.
关于诺拉  我沿着的是这条路
With Nora, I am following down this track.
你知道我追查了多少个
Do you know how many stories I've chased
毫无结果的故事吗
that went absolutely nowhere?
多到我不得不停下来一切
So many that I stopped chasing them for a while
而不是做我本该做的事
instead of doing what I should have done,
实际上  用你的建议
something you suggested, actually,
就是去走一条不同的路
which is going down a different track.
那条路是错的
That track is the wrong one.
小心你的单片眼镜
Careful with your little monocle.
像其他人一样学会记笔记
Learn to take notes like everyone else.
诺拉
Nora!
我的天
Oh, my goodness.
你想干什么  拉尔夫
What do you want, Ralph?
我知道  你为什么害怕解药
I know it's none of my business
并不关我的事
why you're afraid of a cure,
但就其价值而言  我也是超能力者
but for what it's worth, I'm a meta,
我完全支持它
and I'm all for it.
和大多数超能力者谈过以后...
And after talking with most of those people out there...
有的人也这么想
So are some of them.
好的  我知道了
Oh, yeah, I can see that.
我只是不懂为什么
I just don't understand why.
这或许能救他们的命
It might save their lives.
对我来说没那么简单
It's not that simple for me.
为什么
Why not?
因为就像并不是诺瓦克找上了蛇
Because, just like Norvock didn't ask for his snake,
凯特琳也没有来找我
Caity didn't ask for me.
所以如果有天她不敢再当超能力者了
So if one day she wakes up scared of being a meta-human
决定要吃那个解药
and decides to take that cure,
不只是她的超能力会消失
her powers don't just disappear.
我也会消失
I do too.
这就是我真正害怕的
That's what I'm really afraid of.
因为如果我走了  谁来保护她呢
'Cause if I'm gone who's going to protect her?
时候到了
It's witching hour.
我懂了你为什么害怕  但是...
I get why you're scared, but...
你要知道  迪沃让你消失的时候
you need to know that when DeVoe made you disappear,
凯特琳想的都是让你回来
all Caitlin talked about was getting you back.
所以或许和你想保护她一样
So maybe as much as you want to protect her,
凯特琳也想保护你
Caitlin wants to protect you, too.
我今晚跟踪了其中三个人  但他们不在那里
I went after three of them tonight and they weren't there.
你通风报信了吗
Did you tip them off?
没有  我发誓
No, I swear.
在斯宾塞用她的超能科技对我干了好事以后
After what that Spencer woman did to me with her meta-tech,
我想让他们都消失
I want them all gone.
-后来怎么了  -那个地检官
- Then what happened? - The D.A.
她已经知道了你的追捕目标
She figured out you're targeting everyone
就是我给你的那张名单
on the list I gave you.
我在联调局的联系人说他们已经找到了那些人
The contact of mine with the Feds says they're being picked up
并要对他们实施保护性拘留
and put into protective custody.
就在今晚
Tonight.
在哪
Where?
博迪屋顶公司  商业及民居
各位  接你们的来了
Boys and girls, your ride's here.
怎么回事
What the hell?
所有人退后
Everybody get back!
多谢  闪电侠
Thank you, Flash,
帮我把他们都集中起来了
for bringing them all to me.
直升机没办法降落了
The chopper's not going to be able to land.
把所有人带到后面去  让他们想办法上飞机
Take everybody out the back and get them on it somehow.
快点
Come on.
不  他交给我
No, he's mine.
好了  我们已经离开抑制领域了
All right, we're out of the dampening field.
肖娜  你能帮忙吗
Shawna, can you help?
大家自力更生吧
Every meta for themselves.
现在怎么办
What now?
我不觉得你们能从我胳膊上跑过去
I don't suppose you can run up my arm, can you?
拉尔夫  你打算怎么做
Ralph, what are you planning to do?
记住  长颈鹿宝宝
Remember, Baby Giraffe,
他们将信仰寄托在你身上
they took a leap of faith with you.
所以我要为他们冒一次险  秀兰
That's why I'm going to take a leap for them, Shirley.
好了  所有人排成一列纵队
All right, everybody. Straight line, single file,
双手环抱
tuck your arms in.
-把飞机开稳点  -收到
- Keep this thing steady. - Roger that.
站这
Stand there!
双手环抱
Tuck your arms.
你赢不了我的
You can't win this fight.
我肯定可以
I bet I can.
我们还没有正式自我介绍过
We haven't been formally introduced.
他们称我为冰霜杀手  让你见识一下原因
They call me Killer Frost. Let me show you why.
冰霜杀手  蹲下
Killer Frost, duck!
-你救了我  -是你先救了他们
- You saved me. - You saved them first.
干得好
Nice work.
我们快点离开吧
Let's get out of here for real!
给他点颜色看看  闪电侠
Give him hell, Flash!
好了  你看  超能力者都走了  好极了
Okay, you see, the metas are on the move. Bravo.
巴里有点不对劲
Something's wrong with Barry.
战服读数
什么
What?
我从来没见过巴里的战服出现过这样的情况
I've never seen these kind of readings from Barry's suit.
他的能量传导超过28.6亿焦耳
He's channeling over 2.86 billion joules of energy.
这相当于三道闪电的能量总和
That's a combined equivalent of--of almost three lightning bolts.
蝉的力量能使他承受一定程度的伤害
Cicada's powers allow him to sustain injury
但这种程度他肯定承受不了
but not that much.
巴里  巴里
Barry. Barry.
他不会停下的
He's not going to stop.
我不会再让你伤害我的女儿了
You're never gonna hurt my daughter again!
爸
Dad!
不要
No.
对不起  我让他逃跑了
Oh, I'm sorry. I let him get away.
不  你唤回了我的理智
No, you brought me back.
好了  联调局已经接收了诺瓦克
Alright, the Feds have processed Norvock
还有其他的超能力者  会给他们新身份
and the other metas, giving them new identities,
大家都安全了
so everybody's safe.
卫星还没有接收到任何无法解释的暗物质
Satellite hasn't registered any unaccounted for dark matter
所以不管德怀尔在哪  他都没在使用匕首
so, wherever Dwyer is, his dagger's not in use.
在被巴里狠揍了一顿之后
Psh, after the beating Barry gave him,
他不可能这么快就能使用那把匕首的
ain't no way he's using that dagger anytime soon.
怎么了  他罪有应得
What? He got what he deserved.
不  我们很欣赏你恢复了状态
Oh, no, I think we appreciate your groove.
而且我认为冰霜杀手和闪电侠的组合
Also I think that Killer Frost and the Flash combination is
足够让德怀尔
enough to maybe have Dwyer
在短期内不想再在这附近出现了
not want to show his face around here any time soon.
爸  你没事吧
Dad, are you okay?
我没事
I'm good.
最重要的是你没事
What matters is that you're okay.
能够重新站起来奔跑的感觉如何
How's it feel to be up and running again?
超级无敌爽
Super frickin' schway.
想知道什么是超级无敌不爽的吗
Uh, wanna know what's not super frickin' schway?
蝉知道具体什么时间和地点
Cicada knowing exactly when and where
我们会进行秘密转移
our secret transport was taking place.
有内鬼  是吧
Mm. Inside job, right?
蝉很明显有内应  只是
Cicada clearly has a inside man, only--
只是到底是谁居然会帮助蝉杀害无辜的人
Only what kind of cop would help Cicada kill innocent people?
马上要找地方检察官塞西尔·霍尔顿谈话的人
One that's going to have to answer to D.A. Cecile Horton.
队长  你找我
Captain, you wanted to see me?
进来
Come on in.
琼斯警官
Officer Jones,
这是从你的硬盘里复制出来的
this was printed off of your hard drive.
蝉正在追杀的超能力者的名单复印件
Copy of the list of metas that Cicada's been pursuing.
有趣的是  我们知道你这周在家获得的
Funny thing, it is the same list that we know you accessed
和这份是一样的
on your home computer just this week.
介不介意告诉我你决定协助支持蝉的原因
Care to tell me why you decided to aid and abet a murderer?
不  不是那样  你不知道你在说什么
No, that's not--you don't know what you're talking about.
真的吗
Really?
一个女人用超能力者科技来控制你的心智
A woman used meta-human tech to take control of your mind.
她使你做出你自己
She made you do things that you were certain
永远不会去做的事
you would never do.
而那吓到你了  对吧
And that frightened you, didn't it?
那吓到你而且使你愤怒
It frightened you and it made you angry,
而你接受了那份愤怒
and you went ahead and you embraced that anger
并让它主导你的每一个举动
and you let it drive your every move.
背叛  复仇
Betrayal. Revenge.
逃跑
Escape.
这个城市的超能力者一点也不尊重人命
The metas in this city have no respect for human life.
他们不配存活在世上
They don't deserve to breathe our air.
你发誓保护这个城市的市民
You swore an oath to protect the citizens of this city.
每一个
Every one of them.
把他带走
Get him out of my sight.
你知道的  你的直觉一直很敏锐
You know, your instincts have always been sharp.
但敏锐到知道他想要逃跑吗
But knowing he was going to try to escape?
我都可以发誓你在读琼西的心
Could have swore you were reading Jonesy's mind.
这是件有趣的事
It's a funny thing, yeah.
自从詹娜出生后  我已经
Since Jenna was born, I've been
会更多地与我内心的感受对话
a lot more in touch with my feelings.
当乔回来时
When Joe gets back,
你们两个将会是成为一对强大的组合
the two of you will be a force to be reckoned with.
我们已经是了
Oh, we already are.
冰霜杀手  你不用这么做的
Killer Frost, you shouldn't have.
这是你从我这里得到的最接近我道歉的  所以
It's the closest you're getting to an apology from me, so...
好吧  也许那就是为什么我可以
Well, maybe that's why I can hear you
不用麦德2.0就听见你
without the M.A.D. 2.0.
或者是因为你不再讨厌我了
Or maybe it's because you've stopped hating me.
我没有讨厌你
I didn't hate you.
我认为你在犯蠢
I thought you were being stupid.
这是有区别的
There's a difference.
你知道我永远也不会服下解药的  对吧
Hey, you know I'd never take that cure, right?
尽管那意味着要跟我共享一个身体
Even if it means sharing a body with me
直到你变老
until you get old and grey?
当然
Of course.
你是我永不愿分割的一部分
You're a part of me that I never want to lose.
我承诺  我会尽我的一切来保护你
I promise, I will do everything I can to protect you.
我也一样  凯特琳
Right back at you, Caity.
现在  不要对我心软
Now, don't get all soft on me,
但我有点东西要给你
but I got you a little something.
去看看冷却器
Check the cooler.
你好  冰霜  是凯特琳啊
Hey, Frosty. Oh, Caitlin.
那是一个里面装着血的冰球吗
Is that a ball of ice with blood inside of it?
我想是冰霜杀手从蝉那里拿来的
I think Killer Frost took it from Cicada.
拉尔夫  这不只是血
Ralph, this isn't just blood.
这是新造超能力者的DNA样本
This is a DNA sample from a recently created meta-human.
-所以冰霜杀手想通了  -对
- So Killer Frost came around. - Yeah.
是的
She did.
我说不要心软
Ugh, I said don't get soft.
开始笔迹分析
Begin handwriting analysis.
检测到2种笔迹
就像我所怀疑的  诺拉·韦斯特·艾伦的日记里
As I suspected, the journal of Nora West Allen
包含了两种不同的笔迹
contains two different types of handwriting.
那么
So...
有个幕后黑手
There is a mastermind behind the scenes.
唯一的问题是
The only question is...
是谁
who?
好吧  47个炸玉米饼是我官方的最高极限
Okay, 47 tacos is officially my limit.
亲爱的  我想那是所有人的最高极限了
I think that's anyone's limit, honey.
一个康复中的急速者得进食
A healing speedster's gotta eat.
痊愈的  爸爸  我很好
Healed, Dad. I'm fine.
我保证
I promise.
明晚再一起吃晚餐吗
Hey, uh, dinner again tomorrow night?
-好  -好  诺拉
- Yeah. - Yeah, Nora? Um...
我只是
I just...
只是想要你知道我们有多爱你
just want you to know how much we love you.
看吧  她回到原来的样子了
See? She's back to her old self.
你也一样
And so are you.
不  我没有
No, I'm not.
事实上  我不认为我会跟原本一样了
In fact, I don't think I'll ever be the same.
所有的一切都让我意识到  我不知道
All of this has made me realize that, I don't know,
我只是  我从来都不知道我有办法
I just--I never knew I was capable of even caring
像在乎诺拉一样在乎一个人
for someone as much as I care about Nora.
我知道
I did.
巴里  我从来没有遇过比你的心胸更宽阔的人
I've never met anyone with a bigger heart than you, Barry.
所以我不惊讶你是位出色的父亲
So it's no surprise to me that you are a fantastic father.
就如同你是个出色的丈夫
Just like you're a fantastic husband.
禅也是位父亲
Cicada's a father, too.
如果打败他的关键是打动他的心
What if the key to defeating him is appealing to his heart?
-我们要怎么做  -拯救他的孩子
- How do we do that? - By saving his child.
我们要让格蕾丝苏醒
We need to wake up Grace.
图片新闻
没有震波的世界
谁是XS